{
    "id": "ce4689e8b3cf49f2ac4732a36642a313",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Come And Cut",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Pull hard and the two pieces will come …………………..",
            "description": "When things come apart, they separate.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "apart",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09a9f9894600488caa2b54a3958d4ccc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I came ………………. an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "To come across somebody is to meet them unexpectedly.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "through",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f5efe6748319441b96778e97f16d3d6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I came ………………. with typhoid last month.",
            "description": "To come down with typhoid is to become sick with typhoid.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d3370f894e454843b66ea77d5eaacf1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The watchman came …………….. with all the evidences he could collect.",
            "description": "To come forward is to volunteer for a task.",
            "answers": [
                "forward",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "205baf5ff912443c94b0c52333a0248f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you want to lose weight, you should cut ……………… cheese and burgers.",
            "description": "To cut back on something is to consume less of it.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "out",
                "down on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1e69c4c23a6f4dcca762c46a7c9151b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had to cut many trees …………….. to build the house.",
            "description": "To cut something down is to make it fall to the ground.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af53f0fb46a849dbbfdae6ce4f17ff59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie cut …………… while I was chatting with her friend.",
            "description": "To cut in is to interrupt.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09c45530a2104a959b7065430cd881a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The air conditioner will cut ……………… when the room temperature reaches 26 degree Celsius.",
            "description": "When a machine or engine cuts in, it starts operating.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "08433e63aa664d7081a83e7641a3f040"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctors cut ……………….. his legs to save his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f11f31d6613848a99c246a1bf2cd071d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The utility company cut ……………… our power supply because we hadn’t paid the bill.",
            "description": "To cut off power is to stop providing it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cda17cef78514e44ac5deea91bf85aac"
        },
        {
            "question": "His parents cut him ………….. when he married against their wishes.",
            "description": "To cut somebody off is to take them out of a will.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef983e06c70a41a698d3f47e68bf3f3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cut these pictures ………………. of a magazine.",
            "description": "To cut something out is to remove it with scissors.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56de4ea39ee54e388401aebd39e28f4d"
        }
    ]
}